Guide to the Wanda Gifford Photographs 1948-1958
Oregon State University Libraries, University Archives
- Numbered Photographs, 1948-1957; Series I; 1946 negatives and 884 prints
  - Cherie and Barry, 0232; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Cherie dancing, 0233; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Lambs in pasture; taken late evening on trip with Zelda, 0234; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Sheep and lambs, 0235; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Cherie reading book to camera, 0236; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Sears herefords, April 2, 1949; 0239; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
    1/100 at F11
  - Bob Sears' herefords in spring pasture, April 2, 1949; 0240; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Herefords in spring pasture (alta fescue), Bob Sears farm, Ankeney Bottom, 0241; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Herefords on spring pasture (alta fescue), Bob Sears farm, April 2, 1949; 0242; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
    F11 at 1/100 sec.
  - Mare and colt, Sears Farm, 0243; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
    Slightly out of focus.
  - Gathering cherry blooms on a spring day, 0246 (Box 4)
  - Cherry Orchard in bloom, near Popcorn Rd., Salem; smokey day, April 10, 1949; 0247; 4 counts print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Just cherry blossoms, 0248; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Beehives in cherry orchard, April 10, 1949; 0249; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    held camera against tree; stopped down; 3 counts
  - Cherry Valley, Salem, Oregon, April 9, 1948; 0250; 3 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    3 counts foreground 6-sky
  - Dog show, left to right: Gloria Bradbury, Delores Buckmiller, Joanne Carr, and Jean Tibbetts, 0252; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
    Photocopy of one of the images in a newpaper clipping.
  - Jean Tibbetts of Portland on court house steps with her collie dog, 0253; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Little girl and her accordion, 0254; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - Halls Ferry Group, 0255; print and 4 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
    3+ counts; burn foot and white dress in
  - Hagedorn family, anniversary reunion, 0256; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
  - St. Johns litter stirrer, close up, 0257; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Mr. and Mrs. St. Johns sanding eggs, Gervais, Oregon, 0258; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Baby white Leghorn chicks in the brooder on the St. Johns Farm, Gervais, Oregon; Mr. St. Johns is a large poultry producer, 0259; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Brooder house and baby chicks, St. Johns Farm, Gervais, Oregon, 0260; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Jack St. Johns operating litter stirrer, Gervais, Oregon, 0261; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
  - Laying house, St. Johns poultry farm, Gervais, Oregon, 0262; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Neuschwander boy with baby chicks, March 25, 1949; 0263; 2 4x5 negatives and oversize mounted print (Box 9, 76)
    I: about 10ft from camera; 1 flash to right on on camera diffused; II: on flash only not diffussed dark shadow under border; sp graphic views
  - John Wm. Chandler, 0264; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
    3 counts; burn in boy's face; 1/50 at F16 sp. press, no 25 wabash
  - Dan B. Roth auctioneer, Albany, Oregon; registered Gurnsey auction at fairgrounds, March 19, 1949; 0265; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    1/50 at F8; 1 flash at camera
  - Erb; paid $370 for calf, 0266; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    1/50 F11
  - Gary A. Thomas buyer, Gervais, Oregon; Consignee R.M. Lyons, Junction City, Oregon, 0267; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    shot at 1/5 at F16; straight 4 counts F8
  - Auction of registered Guernseys, fairgrounds, March 19, 1949; 0268; 5 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    burn in top; burn in man and foreground; shade the center; 4 counts for center as it is shaded; 1/50 F11 about 25 ft away
  - Wm. Duda, Mt. Angel, Oregon, 0269; 4 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    4 counts overall shading upper part all time (?) (?) on (?); 2 extra counts for foreground only; 2 extra counts for head only; 1/50 F11 25 ft away
  - Interior views, Consolidated Freightways warehouse, March 25, 1949; 0270; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
    F32; painting; 45 counts for lights overhead; wide angle lens
  - Exterior views, Consolidated Freightways warehouse, March 25, 1949; 0271; 3 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
    1/25 at F22; nice day; s.p. press; view camera; K1 filter
  - H.E. Nood; across from Esther Winkley on tractor using manure spreader to shovel gravels (dark day; no filter), 0272; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Norman Reiling, Rt. 1 Hubbard, in stand of alta fescue, April 2, 1949; 0273; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
    Both images available online; view 1; view 2; 4 counts foreground; 3 more sky; no 2 paper
  - Norman Reiling cultivating alta fescue, April 1, 1949; 0274; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
    4 counts foreground 2 more sky
  - Pigs on Roy Love farm, Woodburn, Oregon Rt. 1 (taken late evening light), 0275; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
    4 counts F8
  - Red barn among oaks on Oakley farm, 0276; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Looking north on High Street, Salem, Oregon; business section in background, 0277; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Norman Reiling's seeder, 0278; 4 prints and 6 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
    Three of the images available online: bottom close-up; top close-up; full view
  - Warren Mulkey crowning queen in high school gym, 0279; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
    s.p. press; s.p. graphic; distance 15 ft; 1/100 at F11
  - Entrance to Berg's Market on Center St., 0280; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    electric eye opens doors; 1/100 at F8; dark day
  - Saddle Club birthday party given by Irwin Ward, 1949; 0285; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
  - Excavation by Ben Oljin on Center St. for new Kres? Building, 0286; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Two old ladies watching Circus, Berg opening, 0287; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Ben Oljin outfit excavating dirt, Center St., 0288; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Marion Electric Store, Salem, Oregon, 0289; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Play Ball, Bush School, 0290; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Batter up, Bush School, 0291; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Waiting transportation (bicycles), 0292; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Race, Bush School, 0293; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Willamette River behind paper mill, 0294; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Woman walking down lane, 0295; 3 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - Oregon State Heating Plant, Salem, Oregon, 0296; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - W.C. McDonald Family hoeing strawberries, Salem, Oregon, April 10, 1949; 0297; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - McDonald child in cherry orchard with dog, April 10, 1949; 0298; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    s.p. graphic; 1/100 F11
  - Home on Wallace Rd., 0299; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Pig judging at fair grounds, 0300; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
  - Cherry orchard as seen from Oakley farm on Popcorn Road, Salem, Oregon, 0301; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Haskins cherry tree, Beaver farm, Salem, Oregon, 0302; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Cherry row; Rollin Beaver farm, 0303; prints and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - View of Salem, Oregon from Beaver farm, 0304; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Valley showing McDonald farm and orchard, Rt. 8, Salem, Oregon, 0305; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
  - Looking across valley from Beaver farm, Rt. 8, showing cherry orchards in bloom, April 1949; 0306; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
    One view has telephone pole in frame.
  - Road scene along cherry route, Popcorn Road, 0307; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - Herefords on Withrow farm, Wallace Rd., Salem, Oregon, 0308; print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - Sheep on spring pasture (partial clouds, etc.), 0309; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - Dairy herd on spring pasture, Johnson farm, Salem, Oregon; regular pasture mix, 0310; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Barn, silo and lake, Wallace Rd., Willamette Valley, 0311; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    print on no 2 paper 5 to 6 counts
  - Lane Bros. farm; raising irrigation pressure tank, 0312; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Merry-go-round, 0313; 3 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
  - Cross in deserted cemetery near Salem; clouds in background, 0314; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Young filbert orchard, 0315; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Mr. and Mrs. T.C. Brewster in strawberry field, Salem, Oregon, 0316; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Field of Marshall variety strawberries, 0317-0318
    - 0317, print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    - 0318, 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Oregon Mounted Posse Group, 0319; print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
    Left to right: Walter Zozel, Mrs. Rhodes, Mr. C.E. Rhodes, Mrs. Matt Vetch, Matt Vetch, and George Arbuckle.
  - Lee Eyerly's $5,000 Palamino Allamar, 0320; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Allamar with Douglas McKay, Governor of Oregon, 0321; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Views of Allamar alone and with Douglas McKay., print and 3 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - John Schmultz home; Mission Bottom Rd., Salem, Oregon, 0322; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Cannery labor party, 0323; 4 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
  - John Schmultz home, 0324; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - John Schmultz home, kids at play, 0325; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Marion County Jersey Cattle Club Group, 0326; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    1/100 at F16; s.g.
  - Strawberry field freshly dusted with lime, 0327; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - 4 tractors at work cutting bent grass, Harry Riches farm, 0332; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
  - Young Jersey heifers at base of Mt. Adams, Henry Caryl farm, Trout Lake, 0333; 3 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Henry Caryl herd; Mt. Adams in background, 0335; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Farmers co-op, Silverton, Oregon; grain stacked, 0336; 120 negative (Box 9)
  - Filling silos at H.A. Barnes farm, Salem, Oregon., 0343; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    Ensilage cutters at work; send to Life magazine.
  - Farmers stacking hay, 0344; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
  - Mt. Adams between pines, 0345; print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - Mt. Adams; Eva in pasture, 0346; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Mt. Adams and White Salmon River; Eva on shore, 0347; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Mt. Adams; fallen tree in foreground, 0348; 5 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - Mt. Adams and White Salmon River; Eva on shore, 0349; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Largest Ponderosa Pine tree, Trout Lake, 0350; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
  - Herefords at base of Mt. Adams, Wash., Henry Carly farm, 0351; 4 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - White Salmon River as seen from bridge; taken at Trout Lake, Washington, 0352; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Sunset and hay stacks near Salem, Oregon, 0353; print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - Cocked grain near Salem, Oregon, 0354; 4 prints and 5 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - YMCA Camp; long shot of pool, 0355; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - YMCA Camp dining room, Silver Creek, 0356; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - YMCA Camp; close up shot of pool, 0357; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Tansy rag weed, 0358; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Road to YMCA camp, 0359; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - YMCA kitchen, 0360; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Irrigating corn, Salem, Oregon, 0361; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Bean fields near Salem, Oregon, 0362; print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - Irrigating mint, 0363; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Irrigating mint; boy in one view, 0364; 4 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - Combining grain; umbrella on tractor, 0365; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Patio fireplace, 0366; 11 prints and 4 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - Tractors cutting bent grasses, 0367; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Onion field; seed heads; onions against sky, 0368; 3 120 negatives (Box 9)
  - Santiam River from new highway; Mrs. Ethel Brown on Britenbush Bridge, 0370; 2 prints and 3 120 negatives (Box 4, 9)
    North Santiam River (370a); Detroit Dam construction (370b)
  - Santiam highway dedication -- ceremony, Breitenbush bridge with Douglas McKay, circa 1949; 0371; 13 prints, 11 4x5 negatives, and 7 120 negatives (Box 4, 9)
    Breitenbush bridge (371a); Guests at Santiam Highway dedication (371b)
  - Men at work; finish coat on outside of Blundell(?) Canning Kitchen, 0372; 4 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
  - Azaleas in Capital Park, Salem, Oregon, 0373; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
  - Bob Coons changing tire on big Pierce Freight Lines truck, 0375; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
    night shot; 22 bulb used.
  - Jerry and Vernon; Jerry had cut his hair, 0376; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
  - Ditch between State Capitol and new office building across Court St., 0377; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Marble workers at work on new state office building, 0378; print and 3 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - Mobile mixer on job at Sears new store garage, 0379; 3 prints and 3 4x5 negatives
  - Fair View Home fire, 0380; 6 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
  - Sears bull, 0381; 7 4x5 negatives (Box 9)
  - Dairy herd in Milton F. Hoyser's pasture, River Rd, near Independence, Oregon, 0382; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    no. 3 paper
  - Dairy cows, Hoyser farm, Independence Rd., 0383; 3 prints and 3 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - Baler at work; John Roth farm, 0384; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Clouds and farm, 0385; 3 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - Dr. Fortner Herefords, Silverton, Oregon, 0386; 7 prints and 6 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - Baled hay in field near Salem, Oregon, 0387; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Pictorial shot; cut and uncut hay; P? Rd., 0388; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - BPW girls on beach at Taft, 0389; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Weighing cherries, 0390; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
  - Loading cherries on truck to haul to brining vats, 0391; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - Stirring (brining?) vats of cherries being made into maraschinos, 0392; 4 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
  - Cows in irrigated pasture, Paulson farm near Hubbard, 0393; print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 4, 9)
    4 counts foreground; 3 extra sky; F8 no 2 paper
  - Cocked grain, 0394; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    4 counts foreground 10 sky
  - Cocked grain, 0395; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    6 counts 14 sky
  - Sunset through trees; hay stacks in background, 0397; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
    3 counts foreground up to 35
  - Mt. Adams & Trout Lake River; Eva on stomach, 0398; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    5F counts no 3 paper
  - Baby and turkeys, Trout Lake, Wash., 0399; print and 4x5 negative (Box 4, 9)
    1/100 F16; no 3 paper F8 3+counts
  - Salem Posse in parade, 0400; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Salem Band in parade, 0401; 4x5 negative (Box 9)
  - Sack server and combine near Silverton, Oregon, Wm. Dybevik, 0402; 3 prints and 4 120 negatives (Box 5, 9)
  - America Legion Parade, Salem, 0403; 3 prints and 12 120 negatives (Box 5, 9)
  - Santiam Bean Festival, 0404; 5 120 negatives (Box 9)
  - Construction on Kress Building, 0405; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 9)
  - State Capitol, 0406; print and 120 negative (Box 5, 9)
  - Highway 99 south of Salem, 0407; 120 negative (Box 9)
  - Girl picking cherries, 0408; 2 prints and 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 9)
  - Sears new store from rear and two views of window display, 0409; 3 120 negatives (Box 10)
  - Dome of Oregon State Capital from Willamette University, 0410; 120 negative (Box 10)
  - Feeding into chopper, Dane Turnridge farm; Clarence King, Boiler man, 0411; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Hol mint on truck; Jim Schwab, print and 4x5 negative; 0412 (Box 5, 10)
  - Hauling mint; Clarence King driving, Brigg Shatton, Leed Maden, Roger and Lewis, 0413A; 3 prints and 3 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Sacks of beans in cannery yard; girls watching beans being unloaded, 0413B; 3 prints and 6 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Mr. Carvels, Mill St., cement fence which looks like wood, 0414; print and 120 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Irrigation of mint on Dane Turnridge farm; distillery in background, 0415; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Mr. Sheffield mowing mint, 0416; 3 prints and 3 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Esther Winkley's registered Duroc Jersey Sow and seven pigs nursing, 0417; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Registered Duroc Sow and seven pigs; man in picture, 0418; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Combining grain at 4 corners with Oliver tractor, 0419; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Silo demonstration, H.A. Barnes, 0420; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Case outfit at H.A. Barnes demonstration, 0421; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Crowd watching silo demonstration, 0422; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Long shot; H.A. Barnes demonstration, 0423; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Group of farmers gather to see new ensilage gathering equipment, H.A. Barnes farm, Salem, Oregon, 0424; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - J.I. Case tractor and pick-up hay chopper machinery demonstration at H.A. Barnes farm, 0425; 2 prints and 9 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Reeding grain near Silverton; tractor and seeder, 0426; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Rhoten and Rhoten turkeys, 0427; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Jersey cattle on irrigated clover pasture near Silverton, 0428; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
    use part of negative
  - Cheryl and Irwin Ward's puppies in trailer, 0429; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Girls picking Royal Ann cherries near Salem, Oregon; these cherries all go to the local canneries to be used as maraschino cherries, 0430; print and 4x5 negative (Box 10)
    no. 2 paper
  - Unloading cherries at Willamette Cherry Growers Co-op, Salem, Oregon, 0431; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Cherry pickers; boys and girl on ladders, 0432; 4 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Hauling cherries with tractor and trailers from orchard, 0433; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Norman Reiling and alta fescue negatives, 0434; 7 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
    Alta fescue on Norman Reiling's farm; Alta fescue on Norman Reiling's farm (close); Norman Reiling looking at his alta fescue field; Alta fescue on Norman Reiling's farm; Norman Reiling with alta fescue plants; Norman Reiling with alta fescue plants; Norman Reiling with alta fescue plants
  - Norman Reiling children, 0435; 5 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
    Norman Reiling's son with bike; Norman Reiling's daughter with bike; Norman Reiling's daughter with dog; Norman Reiling's daughter with dog; Norman Reiling's daughters with dog
  - Bob Sears with bull and Roberta Sears with bull, 0436; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Beach combers at Taft, Oregon, 0437; 3 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Prize winners and their lambs at the Turner Fat Lamb Show, 1949; 0439; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Trade Winds fleet at Depoe Bay; boat coming in channel, 0440; print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Bob Sears herefords, 0441; 13 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Tunnel under Court St., 0442; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Fishing on rocks near Depoe Bay, Oregon, 0443; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Ducks on pond, 0444; 2 prints and 3 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Strawberry pickers; close up of little girl; and her sister, 0445; print and 3 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Donald Farmers Co-op, Donald, Oregon, 0446; print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Chester White pigs in barn lot; Reiling farm, Hubbard, Oregon, 0447; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Phylis crocheting, 0448; 3 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Trained dogs corral sheep at Turner Fat Lamb Show, 0449; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Jersey herd, artificially bred; Gordan James farm, Portland Rd, 0450; 3 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - BPW Club at Taft outing, 0451; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Chase turkeys; range, house, watering, and other views, 0452; 8 prints and 7 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Libeck horse negatives, 0453; 9 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Jim Engdahl taking picture, 0454.1; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Little girl drinks at fountain, 0454.2; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Flax negatives at Pen. (Pendleton?), Oregon, 0455; 4 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Grand Champion Seiner heifer Holesten Calf. owned by Kenneth Runnion of Childrens Farm Home, Corvallis, Oregon; calf name: Lilly Bell, sire: Hall Rose Mike dam: numbers, 0457; 1 print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Grand Champion Brown Swiss Bull, 4 years old (Curtis Candy Signal Best) name; owned by E.E. Bones of Toledo, Washington; taken in ring, 0458; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Grand Champion Red Poll Bull owned by Kehne Waln, Salem, Oregon, 0459; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Grand Champion Brown Swiss Bull owned by E.E. Bones of Toledo, Washington (taken with flash inside barns), 0460; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Grand Champion Hereford Bull, 9 months old, 1949 State Fair; owned by M.M. Ranch, Adams, Oregon, 0461; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Chester White Sow and litter owned by A.A. Nofziger, Silverton, Oregon, 0462; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
    flash shot
  - Linn County first prize Jersey calves, 4-H, 0463; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - First place Junior Guernsey Cow owned by Richard Reyne, McMinnville, Oregon, 0464; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Group of Guernsey calves at State Fair; 1st place on left, 0465; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - 4 year old Jersey cow; Richard Johnston won Grand Champ in showmanship, 0466; 120 negative and print (Box 5, 10)
  - Bill Shaw waters the Grand Champs Chester White Sow owned by Glen Hawkins of Shedd, Oregon, 0467; print and 120 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Registered Jersey Cow over 2 years 1st place St. Maus Bollina Bess, owned by Gene Nygren, Albany, Oregon, 0468; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Junior Yearling Guernsey owned by Jimmie Gorman, Crabtree, Oregon; took first place, 0469; print and 120 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Senior Jersey Calf, 4-H Club, first place; owned by Eugene Shrew, Astoria, Oregon, 0470; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Ronald Melott, Hillsboro, Oregon; Junior Jersey Calf, 4-H Club, first place blue ribbon, 0471; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - First place winners all classes Jersey 4-H group, 0472; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - First place winners all classes Jersey 4-H group (Box 5)
    Similar to image 0472.
  - 4-H girls and boys with their Jersey calves, State Fair, 0473; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Guernsey Senior Heifer, first place winner; owned by Robert H. Reed, Sheridan, Oregon, 0474; 3 prints and 2 120 negatives (Box 5)
  - Virginia Gritton, 0475; 4 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Edwards home on Pringle Rd. (graphic view K2 filter, 0476; 3 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Florence Crosby registers, 0477; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Sheep shearing contest at State Fair, 0478; print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Swirly Clouds, 0479; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Road to Steens Mountain (scenic), 0480; 3 120 negatives and 1 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Mary Kueny Ranch and Mary at gate, 0481; 2 prints and 3 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Group at cabin, Mary Kueny Ranch, 0482; 3 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Ira skinning deer, 0483.1; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Ira at cabin door, 0483.2; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Mary's cabin in Steens Mountain, 0484; 3 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Mary and Esther at gate; Mary unharnessing horses; Mary on horse, 0485; 3 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Fields with mountains in background, 0486; print and 5 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Views near cabin at Mary's, 0487; 4 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Five deer in row, 0488; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Harry Winkley and his deer, 0489; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Esther with deer on horse, 0490.1; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Jerry and Harry with deer; home place, 0490.2; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Harry and boys bringing deer out of canyon, 0491; 3 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Skinning deer on side of cabin, 0492; 3 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Men with horses, 0493a; 4x5 negative (Box 10)